veggieboards.com 2004-06-03

# VeggieBoards - Vegetarian and Vegan Board and Forum - Links, Cruelty-freee Shopping, Animal Rights and WelfareGroups

**Privacy Policy**

VeggieBoards values your privacy. To keep you informed, we have created this privacy statement that discloses our purposes and methods for online collection and use of information. This policy applies to all information collected throughout the VeggieBoards website and information gathered from any web pages that we host. 

VeggieBoards contains many links to external sites. We are not responsible for these sites. We try to ensure that all sites that we link to are suitable for our audience. 

_Disclosure of Information_

VeggieBoards will never sell or distribute your email address or other personally identifiable information to third parties without your prior consent. All reasonable care is taken to ensure its security both offline and online. 

We reserve the right to distribute any information on our servers if required to do so by law, or upon order of a court of law. 

It�s also important to be aware that when you voluntarily provide personal information (e.g., address, phone number, photos, etc.), that information is publicly available to both registered members and (in some cases) guests and may be used in a manner in which it was not intended. For that reason, we encourage using caution before offering any personally identifiable information. 

_Statistics and Counters_

When you browse this site, we collect certain non-personal information about your visit. This information includes the following: 

  * The operating system you are using (ex.: Windows XP). 
  * The type of browser you are using (ex.: Microsoft Internet Explorer 6). 
  * The resolution of your screen (ex.: 800x600). 
  * The color resolution of your screen (ex.: 256 colors). 

This information is collected so that we can better design our site to be suitable for our audience. Certain aspects of web design will only work with certain browsers or screen resolutions. 

_Registration at VeggieBoards_

To fully utilize the features of this site, you will need to register. Registration allows members to post in the forums, post comments and upload photos to the photo album, and to use the built-in private messaging system within the forums. 

To register at this site the only personal information we require is a valid email address. This helps us to protect our community from abusive postings and provides a verifiable point of contact should legal questions arise. Your e-mail address is never available to other members. Members can e-mail you through a form on our website and your e-mail address is only revealed if you chose to write them back. If you wish to disable the ability for members to contact you in this manner you can do so at any time through your user CP. 

You also have the option of providing some additional information (e.g., location, occupation, website address, IM name(s), etc.). This information is made available to other members to foster a sense of community. These fields are optional. If you have any concerns about providing this information, simply leave the fields blank. 

Guests are free to search and view select portions of the forums. Guests can not view the photo album. 

_Using the Forums_

All information that you post in the forums is voluntary. As stated above, the only information we require for you to participate in the forums is a valid email address. You have the option in your user cp to hide your email address and/or disable private messaging if you do not wish to be contacted by other members of the site. 

_Personal Messaging System_

The Personal Messaging system is a facility only available to registered members of VeggieBoards. Personal messages are stored on our server. We will not open your personal messaging folders except to investigate a report of abuse, to protect our servers, or if required to do so by law. 

_Cookies_

This website does use cookies to enhance the service we provide. A cookie is a small data file stored on your computer's hard drive. The cookie stores information such as the date you last visited the site. This allows the site to recognize your username and automatically mark new posts and threads in the forums since your last visit. There is an option in your user cp to disable the use of cookies. Most browsers can be set to not accept cookies. 

For more information about cookies, please see: 

_IP Addresses_

When you post in the forums your IP address is logged. This IP address is unique to your internet connection and is provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). Your IP address is only visible to our admin and moderators. It is used as a security measure to prevent abuse of our forums and website. In exceptional circumstances we may be required to report abusive members to their ISP for further action. 

For more information about IP addresses, please see: 

_Advertising Servers_

To help to pay for this site we use advertising. We periodically use the following advertising companies to provide some of our advertisements: 

It has been brought to our attention that some of these networks may use cookies in conjunction with their ads. We would advise you to read the privacy statements of each of these companies and contact them if you have any concerns. VeggieBoards does not use cookies with any of the advertisements served from our server. 

_Right to Change Policy_

As we are constantly adding new features to VeggieBoards, we reserve the right to update our privacy policy to reflect these new services. As the policy is updated, the date at the top will be changed to reflect this. By using this site, you agree to be bound by the modifications or updates to this Privacy Policy. 

_Updating Your Information_

All information in your personal profile can be updated by selecting the appropriate tab in your user cp. 

_Contacting Us_

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to [contact us](mailto:veggieboards@verizon.net?subject=Privacy_Policy). 

Originally Posted: November 16, 2003.  
Last Update: December 27, 2003.
